this is knit with logos by Nick comm and
这是尼克·科姆用标志编织的
in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create your own custom color
如何创建您自己的定制颜色
palettes in Inkscape and save them to
Inkscape中的调色板并将其保存到
your installation so that you can load
您的安装，以便您可以加载
them up and work with them at any point
在任何时候与他们一起工作
in the future if you'd like and if you'd
在未来，如果你愿意，如果你
like to learn more about how Inkscape
我想了解更多关于Inkscape如何
works be sure to check out my Inkscape
作品请务必查看我的Inkscape
masterclass it's a collection of over 60
大师班，这是一个超过60件的收藏
videos where I go over every tool in
我在其中查看每个工具的视频
future in Inkscape and I explain what it
Inkscape的未来，我解释它是什么
is and demonstrate how it works I'll
并演示它的工作原理，我将
have a link in the description of the
在描述中有一个链接
video if you want to check that out so
视频，如果您想要查看的话
to get us started here as you can see I
让我们在这里开始，正如你所见，我
have Inkscape opened up on my screen and
在我的屏幕上打开Inkscape
if you look down here to the bottom of
如果你从这里往下看到底部
the page you'll notice we have this
你会注意到我们有这样一个页面
color palette that we normally work with
我们通常使用的调色板
an Inkscape and if you click this little
一个Inkscape，如果你点击这个小
arrow icon over here to the bottom right
右下角的箭头图标
you'll get this little flyout menu with
您将看到这个小弹出菜单，其中包含
a bunch of different color palettes to
一堆不同的调色板
choose from now by default
默认情况下从现在开始选择
Inkscape has the Inkscape default
Inkscape具有默认的Inkscape
palette here when you load it up but you
这里的调色板，当您加载它时，但您
can choose from any of these other
可以从这些其他选项中进行选择
options here like for example if you
此处的选项，例如，如果您
click on greens it'll give you a wide
点击绿色，它会给你一个宽阔的
spectrum of green shades to choose from
可供选择的绿色色调光谱
and coloring your objects and there's a
并给你的物体上色，而且有一个
whole bunch of different options in here
这里有一大堆不同的选择
if you want to check it out you can look
如果你想去看看，你可以去看看
at something like a bun sue here where
在像面包这样的东西上
this looks as if it's the Ubuntu
这看起来像是Ubuntu
branding colors so on and so forth now
现在的品牌颜色等等
what you can do is you can actually
你能做的是，你实际上可以
create your own color palette and add it
创建您自己的调色板并添加它
to this list using the technique I'm
使用我正在使用的技术添加到这个列表
going to show you in this tutorial so
在本教程中，我将向您展示
let me set this back to Inkscape default
让我将其设置回Inkscape默认设置
for now
就目前而言
and let me just set up the document here
让我在这里设置文档
I'm gonna go to file document properties
我要去归档文档属性
and I want to turn off the visibility of
我想要关闭能见度
the page border for now so where it says
现在的页面边框是这样写的
show page border just deselect that for
显示页面边框只需取消选中该选项即可
now and I'm gonna come up here to the
现在我要走到这里来
grids tab and I'm going to add a new
“网格”选项卡，我要添加一个新的
rectangular grid click on new and where
在矩形网格上单击新建和位置
it says spacing X and space and Y I'm
上面写着空格X和空格Y我是
going to change each of those to 100 so
我要把每一个都改成100个
that there's 100 pixels of space between
它们之间有100个像素的空间
each grid line close out of that we're
每一条网格线都离得很近
gonna go to view zoom zoom in at 1 to 1
我要去查看1比1的放大
so that we have a 100% view of the
这样我们就能100%地看到
document here and then finally I'm going
在这里记录，然后最后我要去
to open up the fill and Stroke menu with
使用打开填充和描边菜单的步骤
this button up here or you can press
这个按钮在上面，或者你可以按
control shift + F on the keyboard so
按住键盘上的Shift+F组合键，以便
what I'm going to do now is I'm
我现在要做的是
basically going to create a bunch of
基本上是要创建一系列
objects and color them all in with
对象，并为它们全部上色
whatever shade
不管是什么颜色
like to be included in my custom color
喜欢包含在我的定制颜色中
palette that I'm gonna load up in here
我要在这里装入的调色板
so I'm going to grab the squares and
所以我要拿起方块，
rectangles tool and I'm going to create
矩形工具和我要创建的
a square within these grid lines and I'm
在这些网格线内的一个正方形，我
going to color this in with a shade that
我要给这个涂上一种深浅的颜色
I would like to save maybe something
我可能想留点什么东西
like that and I'm going to create
就像这样，我要创造
another shade I would like to save maybe
也许我想保留另一种色调。
something like that then create
这样的东西就会创造出
something else maybe something like that
其他的，可能是类似的东西
that's looking pretty good
看起来挺不错的
and we're going to do is I'm just going
我们要做的就是我要去
to go through and I'm gonna create a
我要创建一个
bunch of different objects and I'm gonna
一堆不同的物体，我要
color them all in with colors that I
把它们都涂上我喜欢的颜色
like that I'd like to save to my custom
像这样，我想保存到我的习惯中。
color palette
调色板
okay so as you can see here I've gone
好的，如你所见，我已经走了
through and I've created a bunch of
我已经创造了一堆
different squares and I've colored them
不同的正方形，我给它们上色
in with colors that I'd like to save to
使用我想保存到的颜色
my palette once I'm finished what I'm
我的调色板一旦我完成了我的工作
going to do is I'm going to click off of
我要做的是，我要关闭
the graphic to deselect everything and
取消选择所有内容的图形和
then I'm gonna come back to the document
然后我会回到文件上
properties by going to file document
属性，通过转到文件文档
properties and let's come back over to
属性，让我们回到
the page tab and I'm going to turn the
页面选项卡，我将把
visibility of the page border back on
页面边框的可见性重新打开
and I'm gonna come over here to where it
我要到这里来，在那里
says resize page to content I'm going to
说将页面大小调整为我要访问的内容
expand to that menu and I'm gonna click
展开到该菜单，我将单击
this button right here that says resize
这里的这个按钮写着调整大小
page to drawing or selection and that we
页面到绘图或选定内容，并且我们
can close out of that menu and that's
可以关闭那个菜单，那就是
gonna do what that's gonna do is it's
我要做的就是这是
gonna make the document size fit the
我将使文档大小适合
size of the graphic that we've created
我们创建的图形的大小
here and all I'm gonna do now is I'm
我现在要做的就是
just gonna save this I'm gonna go to
我要留着这个，我要去
file save as and for now I'm just gonna
文件另存为，现在我只想
save this to my desktop I'm going to
把这个保存到我的桌面上，我要
give it whatever name I'd like the name
给它起任何我想要的名字
of the color palette to be in this list
此列表中要使用的调色板的
when I bring it up so I'm just gonna for
当我提起这件事的时候，我只想
demonstration purpose isms going to name
演示目的主义将命名
this u2 palette and I'm actually going
这个U2调色板和我实际上
to save this I'm not going to save this
为了保存这个，我不会保存这个
as an SVG file I'm going to save it as a
作为SVG文件，我打算将其另存为
dot GPL file or a palette file and
点GPL文件或调色板文件以及
I'm gonna go ahead and click Save now
我将继续并单击立即保存
let me close out of Inkscape here let me
让我在这里关闭Inkscape让我
minimize this what we have over here I
最小化这一点，我们在这里有
have this on my desktop this is the GPL
把这个放在我的桌面上这是GPL
file I'm going to open up a window I'm
我要打开一扇窗，我要
actually gonna open up a folder and go
实际上我要打开一个文件夹，然后
to wherever it is that you have your
无论你在哪里都有你的
Inkscape whatever Drive that you have
Inkscape无论您拥有什么驱动器
Inkscape installed on for most of you is
安装了Inkscape的大多数人都是
probably going to be your C Drive for me
可能会成为我的C盘
I have it saved on my e Drive so I'm
我把它保存在我的e驱动器上，所以我
gonna open up the e Drive
我要打开e车道
I'm gonna look for Program Files I'm
我要去找我的程序文件
gonna go to Inkscape share Inkscape and
我要转到Inkscape共享Inkscape和
palettes and if you noticed here we have
调色板，如果你注意到这里，我们有
an index of all of our color palettes
我们所有调色板的索引
that are included with our Inkscape
包含在我们的Inkscape中
installation so I'm just going to take
安装，所以我要把
this YouTube palette GPL and click and
此YouTube调色板GPL并点击和
drag this into the folder go ahead and
将此文件拖到文件夹中，然后
click continue to give it permission to
单击继续授予其权限以执行以下操作
do so and all we have to do now is
这样做，我们现在要做的就是
restart Inkscape so let me come back up
重新启动Inkscape，让我重新启动
here let me close out of Inkscape
在这里，让我结束Inkscape
and let me just load it back up make it
让我把它装回去，让它
fullscreen there we go and let's click
全屏显示，然后点击
on this arrow again and there you go
再次沿着这个箭头，就这样了
YouTube padlet the GPL if you click on
如果您点击，YouTube Padlet即可使用GPT
that there is our custom color palette
有我们自定义的调色板
based on those colors that I used in
基于我使用的那些颜色
that previous document you can now color
您现在可以为之前的文档上色
this in however you would like so I
无论你想怎样，所以我
think that should do it for today's
我认为今天应该就够了
tutorial that is how you can go about
教程，这是您可以如何进行
creating your own custom color palettes
创建您自己的自定义调色板
in Inkscape and saving them so that you
在Inkscape中保存它们，以便您
can work with them in the future if you
如果您将来可以与他们合作
have any questions leave a comment below
有任何问题请在下面留言
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]